# CHRISTINA XAMIN

#### CONTACT

cxamin@gmail.com



(416)-523-3132



www.christinaxamin.com

Oakville, ON, Canada

#### SKILLS

- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite
- Confident working with both Macs and PCs, as well as their accompanying software (Microsoft Office, iWork, etc.)
- Understanding of HTML. CSS, and JavaScript
- Team player with excellent communication skills
- Excels using prototyping software including Adobe XD, Sketch and InVision
- Able to make decisions and work through problems
- Manages time effectively
- Easily adapts to new situations
- Presents ideas and opinions in an open and unbiased way
- Comfortable engaging with stakeholders to gather data and requirements
- Able to map user journeys through to completion

Ambitious designer with 6+ years experience in a professional design environment and a Bachelor of Interaction Design degree. Highly proficient in graphic design, video editing and web design software. Background in visual and creative arts using both traditional and digital elements.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor of Interaction Design** Sheridan College

September 2014 - April 2018

## **Visual and Creative Arts Advanced Diploma** Sheridan College

January 2012 - May 2014

#### EXPERIENCE

## **USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER** Surrey Place, Toronto, ON

August 2018- Present

- Interviewed stakeholders (including partners and end users) to gather and determine requirements
- Developed wireframes and prototypes based on user research then implemented usability testing for project development
- Successfully provided research and recommendations on multiple projects to meet web accessibility compliance

## INTERACTIVE AND TECHNICAL MEDIA WRITER INTERN Rapid7, Toronto, ON

May 2017- September 2017

- Guided users through UI by contributing to company's software help documentation
- Collaborated with multiple teams to create documents that outlined in-product features

## GRAPHIC DESIGN ASSISTANT (CONTRACT) Oakville Public Library, Oakville, ON

May 2016- August 2016

- · Created various promotional material for print, web and environmental applications
- Maintained a graphic consistency by adhering to the library's visual identity and AODA compliancy